livepages.com.au 2018-08-12

# PRIVACY POLICY

Welcome to Live Pages.com.au Pty Ltd ("Live Pages") Privacy Policy. Your privacy is very important to us. You must read and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy before accessing or using livepages.com.au ("Website"). This Privacy Policy governs the information we collect about you, the use and disclosure of information. By accepting this Privacy Policy, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy.

**Interpretation**

In these terms and conditions, the expressions "we", "us" and "our" are references to Live Pages.

**Information We Collect**

We collect personal information when we provide our services to you. Generally we will tell you why we are collecting information when we collect it and how we plan to use it or these things will be obvious when we collect the information.

We use a feature of internet web browsers called a "Cookie" which enable us to monitor traffic patterns and to serve you more efficiently if you revisit the site. A Cookie does not identify you personally but it does identify your computer. Cookies are small files placed on your hard drive that assist us in providing customised services. We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of a Cookie. Cookies can also help us provide information which is targeted to your interests. You are always free to decline our Cookies if your browser permits, although in that case you may not be able to use certain features on our Website and you may be required to reenter your password more frequently during a session.

In addition, each time you use the Website, we will collect general usage information from you including, types of searches, the date your searches are performed and the number of searches you make.

All personal information which we collect (including your contact details and, if relevant, credit card details) is kept confidential to the best of our ability. You will appreciate, however, that we cannot guarantee the security of transmission.

If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Website, we may collect such information into a file specific to you.

**Use of Information**

Generally the collected information is to provide you with a tailored, efficient, safer and personalized experience in accordance with your preferences, as well as for customer support purposes. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs, and to customise our services to make your experience safer and easier. The information will help us better understand how Live Pages is being used and will assist us in continuing to improve our services.

As part of the normal operation of our services, we may share certain information about you with selected business partners from time to time, including those who may offer services that complement those provided by us or which we believe may be of interest to you. For example, we may engage third parties to make improvements on our Website, and to assist us in improving our products and services and to offer new products and services. If we do this we generally require these parties to protect your information in the same way we do.

If you request us not to use personal information in a particular manner or at all, we will adopt all reasonable measures to observe your request but we may still use or disclose that information if:

we subsequently notify you of the intended use or disclosure and you do not object to that use or disclosure;

we believe that the use or disclosure is reasonably necessary to assist a law enforcement agency or an agency responsible for government or public security in the performance of their functions; or

we are required by law to disclose the information.

We will preserve the content of any email you send us if we believe we have the legal requirement to do so. Your email message content may be monitored by us for trouble-shooting or maintenance purposes or if any form of email abuse is suspected.

**Questionnaires and Surveys**

From time to time, we may ask you to complete questionnaires or surveys, which we use to obtain additional demographic information about our users, to measure and improve the quality of our service and to better assess your interests and needs. If we ask you to complete a survey or questionnaire, we will explain how we intend to use the information that you provide to us. You always have the option of not responding to any questionnaire or survey.

**Aggregated General Information**

In addition, we may share aggregated general information with our business partners or the general public. For example, we may share information regarding the daily number of unique users to our Website with potential advertisers or others. Aggregated data does not contain any information that could be used to contact or identify you.

**Children**

Children (persons under the age of 18 years) are not eligible to use our services unsupervised. If you are under the age of 18 years, you can use this service only in conjunction with and under the supervision of your parents or guardians. Nevertheless it is our policy not to require personal information from persons known to be under the age of 18 years or offer to send any promotional material to persons in that category.

You are entitled to have access to any personal information relating to you which you have previously supplied to us over this Website. You are entitled to edit or delete such information unless we are required by law to retain it.

**Linked Internet Websites**

The Website provides hyperlinks, which are highlighted words or pictures within a hypertext document that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document or to another document altogether, to other Websites not controlled by us. These hyperlinked Websites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected by these websites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

**Security**

We strive to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information of our users. Although we use industry standard practices to protect your personal information, due to technical limitations, we cannot and do not guarantee, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. We make no representations or warranties with regard to the sufficiency of these security measures.

**Sale of Assets**

In the event that another company or entity acquires all or substantially all of the assets of Live Pages, we reserve the right to include personally identifiable information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company or entity.

**Amendments to Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time to reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. Any amendments made to this Privacy Policy will be considered effective ten (10) days after the amendments are posted on this Website. If you do not agree to such changes, upon your request, we will deactivate your account, contact information, and financial information (if any) from our active databases. Such information will be deactivated as soon as reasonably possible in accordance with our deactivation policy and applicable law. We will however, retain in our files, information you have requested to remove in some circumstances, such as to prevent fraud, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, and to enforce any terms and conditions, and to comply with legal requirements. Further, such prior information is never completely removed from our databases due to technical constraints and the fact that we back up our systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.

**Comments and Inquiries**

We appreciate any comments you may have on our Website, or ideas you may have on how to improve our Website. Comments and questions concerning this Website, or any aspect of this Privacy Policy may be directed to Live Pages at PO Box 1553, Chatswood NSW, 2057 or emailing [info@livepages.com.au](mailto:info@livepages.com.au).
